const Sports = [
    {
      "question": "Who won the World Cup in 2010 ?",
      "answers": ["Spain", "Brazil", "United States", "Netherlands"],
      "correctAnswer": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "Currently in 2014 who is the highest paid athlete at 78.1 million ?",
      "answers": ["LeBron James", "Tiger Woods", "Roger Federer", "Kobe Bryant"],
      "correctAnswer": 1
    },

    {
      "question": "What sport would you be playing if you were using a mallet ?",
      "answers": ["Lacrosse ", "Pool", "Golf", "Polo"],
      "correctAnswer": 3
    },

    {
      "question": "In a standard 8-ball game of pool, how many balls are needed to play ?",
      "answers": ["16", "8", "9", "15"],
      "correctAnswer": 0
    },

    {
      "question": "How many strikes make a perfect game in bowling ?",
      "answers": [
        "11",
        "10",
        "12",
        "13"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": 2
    }
  ]
const Kids = [
  {
    "question": "What is the province that starts with the letter O?",
    "answers": ["Ontario", "New Brunswick", "Manitoba", "Quebec"],
    "correctAnswer": 0
  },

  {
    "question": "What province begins with the letter Q?",
    "answers": ["Ontario", "New Brunswick", "Nova Scotia", "Quebec"],
    "correctAnswer": 3
  },

  {
    "question": "Which of these provinces start with 'New'?",
    "answers": ["Ontario", "New Brunswick", "Quebec", "Manitoba"],
    "correctAnswer": 1
  },

  {
    "question": "Which of these begin with the word 'Man'?",
    "answers": ["Ontario", "New Brunswick", "Quebec", "Manitoba"],
    "correctAnswer": 3
  },

  {
    "question": "Which of these begin with the word 'Nova'?",
    "answers": [
      "Ontario",
      "Nova Scotia",
      "British Columbia",
      "New Brunswick"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": 1
  }
]
const History = [
  {
    "question": "Which movie is famous for the line 'Say hello to my little friend' ?",
    "answers": ["The Godfather", "Scarface", "American Gangster", "Bugsy"],
    "correctAnswer": 1
  },

  {
    "question": "In what year was the first Friday the 13th released ?",
    "answers": ["1980", "1975", "1985", "1990"],
    "correctAnswer": 0
  },

  {
    "question": "In this Nicolas Cage movie he can see two minutes into his future ?",
    "answers": ["The Wicker Man", "Next", "Knowing", "Season of the Witch"],
    "correctAnswer": 1
  },

  {
    "question": "Which movie starts with a police officer and his daughter touring the White House ?",
    "answers": ["Olympus Has Fallen", "Air Force One", "Murder at 1600", "White House Down"],
    "correctAnswer": 3
  },

  {
    "question": "Which is not an important rule to remember for a Mogwai ?",
    "answers": [
      "Never expose it to bright light",
      "Never feed it after midnight",
      "Never pet it",
      "Never get it wet"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": 2
  }
]
const Geography = [
  {
    "question": "Where is the Amazon Rainforest ?",
    "answers": ["South America", "Africa", "Asia", "Australia"],
    "correctAnswer": 0
  },

  {
    "question": "What is the captial of Jamaica ?",
    "answers": ["Portmore", "Linstead", "Kingston", "Montego Bay"],
    "correctAnswer": 2
  },

  {
    "question": "Which contry does not boarder the Black Sea ?",
    "answers": ["Turkey", "Romania", "Bulgaria", "Hungary"],
    "correctAnswer": 3
  },

  {
    "question": "Which is the longest river ?",
    "answers": ["Orange River", "Nile", "Congo River", "Zambezi"],
    "correctAnswer": 1
  },

  {
    "question": "Of the states listed, which is the largest in size ?",
    "answers": [
      "Montana",
      "Colorado",
      "California",
      "New Mexico"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": 2
  }
]

export {Kids, Sports, History, Geography}